

### **HASSAN ZIHMMOU**

3D Generalist, Motion Designer, 2D & 3D Animator zihmmouhassan@gmail.com

LINKS

WebSite: www.hassanzihmmou.com

## CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a CG Generalist with 10 years of experience in 3D and 2D animation, frame-by-frame animation, and motion graphics.

Currently, I am an animator at a production company where I am in charge of animating four episodes of a court animated series.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **NEVERSEEN**

Production agency | Freelance (Remote)

3D animator and Rigger.

- Animating four episodes of a court animated series.

| Oct 2023 - Present | Morocco

#### **INVESTOR BRANDS**

Niche Agency | Full Time (Remote)

Character Rigger and animator

- 3D Character Rigging and Animation using Mocaps and keyFrame animation.
- Rendering in Unreal Engine and Compositing.

| May 2022 - Oct 2023 | United Kingdom

#### **ABWEB**

Digital Agency | Full Time (Hybrid)

2D Graphic and Motion Designer.

| June 2018 - May 2022 | Morocco, Casablanca

#### **IMAGE FACTORY**

Production & Post Production Agency | Full Time (On-site)

CG GENERALIST, 2D/3D ANIMATOR, VFX COMPOSITOR.

- CG Generalist, 3D animator and compositor on Tv commercials and Series.
- CG Generalist, 3D animator and compositior on Movies.
- 2D flash animator, Logo design, storyboard.

| May 2014 - June 2018 | Morocco, Casablanca

	_		
EDUCATION	INFODESIGN		
	Bachelor's in Secondary z.   May 2012 - June 2014   Casablanca, Morocco		
	Conversational	Conversational	Native
KILLS	MAYA, Mudbox, Un	real Engine, AfterEffects	s, Premier, Photoshop, Animate, Illustrator.
	Modelling, uv editing, texturing, rigging, 3D animation, Compositing, Rendering, 2D		
	animation, Frame I	by Frame animation.	